ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Atelier-7, 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Automatic Board Meeting Corporation, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Automatic Embroideries, 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Automatic Stitching, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- B&H Apparel Company, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Barcraft, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Barcraft of California, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Bel-Air Belt Company, 1957-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Belasco Belt Company, 1960-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Beltline of California, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Better Made Tucking Company, 1949-1958 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Biltmore Artcraft, 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Blakeslee Manufacturing Company, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Bob G. Lee Company, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Bouquet Fashions, 1966-1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Braemar Coat Company, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- California Apparel Accessories Agreement and Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- California Apparel Contracts, 1951-1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- California Apparel Accessory Belt, 1953-1958 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- California Bias Binding, 1958-1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- California Dress and Sportswear Membership, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- California Novelty Company, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- California Pleating Company, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- California Schiffli Company, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- California Skirt, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Bernard Cowen, 1959-1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Antaky Quilting, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Bronson of California, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association, 1953-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cappi Originals, 1953-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Capri Coats, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Carmen Porras, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chana Baker, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Chic Belt of California, 1966-1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Classic Belt, 1951-1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Contessa of California, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Creative Embroidery, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- D'Andre, Incorporated, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- D'Anna of California, 1963-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- D&M Fashions, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- D&M Fashions, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Daches Embroidery, 1958-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Danica Clothing, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Danica Clothing Company, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Dave Seiman Dress Company, 1959-1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Davis Pleating and Button Company, 1958-1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Deanna Dee, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Deantogs of California, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- De Graff of California, Incorporated, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- DeGraff of California, Incorporated, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- DeGraff of California, Incorporated, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Dumaz Brothers and Canez, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Dumas of California, 1955-1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Edith Small, Incorporated, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- El-Jo Styles, Incorporated, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Elena's Better Dresses, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Ellsworth, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Ernest Strauss, Incorporated, 1965-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Ernst Strauss Incorporated, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Ernst Strauss, Incorporated, 1964-1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Deanna Dee, 1965-1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Ferrara of California, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Francisco Almar Corporation, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Frederick Knits, 1953-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Fredley of California, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Ivan Fredericks of California, 1948-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- F&K, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- F&L, 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Fashion Craft, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Fashion Mate of California, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Fashion Craft, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Fashion Sportswear, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Fashion Sportswear, 1957-1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Germaine Bouffard, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- G&G Sportswear, 1964-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Gold Brothers, Incorporated, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Gold Brothers, Incorporated, 1965-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Gold Brothers, Incorporated, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Harrod's of California, 1949-1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Harry Schneider, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Harry Schneider, 1965-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Hartfield-Zodys, Incorporated, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Helene Button Company, 1958-1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- H&M Sportswear, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- I&D and I&M Sportswear, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- H.M.V. Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- I&D Sportswear, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Hollywood Casuals, 1948-1971 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Ideal Dress and Sportswear, 1949-1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- I.J. Wexter Coats, 1961-1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- I.J. Wexler Company, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- I.J. Wexler Coats, 1959-1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Jan-De-Lee Garment Manufacturing Company, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Jan-Dea-Lee Manufacturing Company, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Jay Lin, 1967-1978 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Jay Vee Sportswear, 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Jenel Sportswear, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Block, Harry: Impartial Chairman, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Holly Stores, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Jay Daniels of California, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Joanna of California, Incorporated, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- J.L. Editions Dress and Sportswear, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joe Accordino, Incorporated, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Jo. L. Fashions, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Junior Flair of California, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Junior Miss: Tabak, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Kahn of California, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kahn of California, 1955-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Kahn of California, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Katy Fashions, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- King Gray Sportswear, 1948-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Klasky Appel, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Klasky Appel, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- L.A. Cloak Joint Board, 1946-1954 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- L.A. Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1948-1959 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- L.K. Shapiro Associates, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- L.K. Shapiro Associates, Incorporated, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Landag Manufacturing Company, 1959-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Landag Manufacturing Company, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Laura of California, 1961-1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Bob Lee Manufacturing Company, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Lee Mar of California, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Lia Coat Company, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Little California Coat Company, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Little California Coat Company, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Lorraine of California, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Lorraine Fashions, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Lorraine Fashions, 1965-1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1948-1960 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Los Angeles Shoulder Pad Company, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Lou Green, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Lou Green, Incorporated, 1955-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Lu-Lan Fashions, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Los Angeles Joint Board of ILGWU: Agreements, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Mad Whirl of California, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Majestic Dress, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Mar-Dor of California, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Mar-Dor of California and L.K. Shapiro, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Michaelson, Incorporated, 1965-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Mari Bella Sportswear, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Marino, John, 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Mercy of California, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Merrill of California, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Mayfair Coat Corporation, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- M&H Sportswear, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- M&H Sportswear, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Michaelson, Incorporated, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Michaelson, Incorporated, 1951-1973 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Smith, Mickey, 1955-1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Miss Scott, 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Monique Sportswear, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Montebello Coat Company, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Mister Dino, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Ontario Garment, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Ontario Garment, Incorporated, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Panorama Garment Company, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Panorama Garment Company, 1967-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Panorama Garment Company, 1960-1975 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Phil and Hy Gold, 1952-1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Shil Socket Manufacturing Company, 1953-1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Philip Originals, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Philip Originals, 1962-1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Rose-Lin of California, 1964-1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Rose-Lin of California, 1967-1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Roth-Le Cover of California, 1969-1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Roth-Le Cover of California, 1949-1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- W. Oppenheimer Company, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Roth-Le Cover of California, 1966-1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Fred Rothschild, Incorporated, 1957-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Ruth E. Lewis and Company, 1958-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Santa Ana Garment Company, 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- San Carlos Coat Company, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Santa Ana Garment Company, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Harry Schneider, Incorporated, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- S. Edelman Embroidery, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Sea Darlings of California, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Sergee of California, 1948-1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- M. Shapiro and Company, 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- M. Shapiro and Company, 1957-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- M. Shapiro and Company, 1969-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Slater Embroidery, 1957-1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Smart Maid Coat Company, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Smart Modes Coat Company, 1965-1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Smart Modes of California, 1966-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Smart Modes of California, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Smart Modes of California, 1951-1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Stanley Nelson, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Stephen Laurie of California, Incorporated, 1949-1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Studio Fashions, 1957-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Style Art of California, 1962-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Style Art of California, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Sun Cal of California, 1969-1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Sun Cal Coat and Suit Company, 1950-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Sun Cal Coat and Suit Company, 1965-1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Susan Deb, Incorporated, 1957-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Tanne, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Teamsters, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Ted Stern Company, 1961-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Tejay Sportswear, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Terri Lee Manufacturing Company, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Terry Tuck, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Trio Coats, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Tuxford Manufacturing, Incorporated, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Vicky "C" of California, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Vita Coats Company, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Volume Merchandise of California, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Volume Merchandise of California, 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Weider of California, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Weider of California, 1959-1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Young Miss of California, 1954-1957 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Master File: Decisions-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Master File: 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Master File: 1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Master File: 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Master File: 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Master File: 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Master File: 1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Master File: 1958 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Master File: 1957 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Master File: 1956 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Master File: 1952 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Master File: 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Master File: 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Master File: 1949 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Master File: 1948 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Master File: 1947 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Financial Records and Contributions to the Office of the Impartial Chairman, 1953-1976 (Box 11.1, Folder 1)
- Congress Workers Group, 1953-1955 (Box 11.1, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association: Agreements, Records and Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 11.1, Folder 3)
- Northern Contracts, 1943-1953 (Box 11.1, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association, 1973 (Box 11.1, Folder 5)
- Benefit Funds, 1966-1970 (Box 11.1, Folder 6)
- The Board of Trustees of the Impartial Chairman's Office, 1967-1972 (Box 11.1, Folder 7)
- Office of the Impartial Chairman: Miscellaneous, 1968-1971 (Box 11.1, Folder 8)
- The Office of the Impartial Chairman: Statements, 1975 (Box 11.1, Folder 9)
- The Office of the Impartial Chairman: Paid Bills, 1975-1977 (Box 11.1, Folder 10)
- Social Security, 1953-1975 (Box 11.1, Folder 11)
- Decisions of Impartial Chairman: Collections Pending, 1967 (Box 11.1, Folder 12)
- Compliance Board Meeting: Minutes, 1965-1974 (Box 11.1, Folder 13)
- Paid Bill, 1969-1978 (Box 11.1, Folder 14)
- ILGWU: General Ledger, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Registrar: Recorder Forms (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Status and Summary Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Stein, Walter: Assistant to President, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Strikebreakers Law, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Strike Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Strike Sanction Request Forms, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Strongin, Paul G.: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Strongin, Paul: ILGWU, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Strongin, Paul: Personal Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund: ILGWU, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Task Force on Goals, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Teamsters, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Telegrams, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Teper, Lezare: Research Department, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Second Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Trophy Company, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Tyler, Gus, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Union Label Department, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Union Security, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- United Organization of Taxpayers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- United States Senate and Congress Correspondence: Answers, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- United States Senate and Congress Correspondence: Requests, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- United States Post Office, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Utah: Industrial Commission, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- United Garment Workers of America, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Standard Form Union Proposal and Request for Information, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- United Farm Workers, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Union Label Department Statement of Receipts and Disbursement, 1973-1980 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Union Label Department: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Wage Claim Settlements, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- United Nations Association, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Cornelius Wall: Incoming Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Cornelius Wall: Personal Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Cornelius Wall: Personal Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Washington County Labor, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Women's Apparel Chains Association, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Women's Wear Daily: Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Agenda for Western States Appeals Committee Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Western States Region: Appeals Committee Meeting Agenda, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Western States Region Executive Committee: Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- William F.T. Wan: Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Wolf and Schulman: Certified Public Accountants, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Wolf, Max B.: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Wolmer, Helen: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Yager, Mitchell, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Xerox Corporation, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Younger, Evelle J.: Attorney Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Electing Unions Officers Handbooks, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- National Center for Immigrants Rights, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Barbizon Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Mode O'Day Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Barbizon of Utah: Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- L.A. Coat and Suit Manufactures Association: Negotiations, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 1979 Settlement: New York (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Newsletter, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Non-Union Shops List: Arizona and Utah, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- NUFIS (Non-Union Firm Information System), 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Non-Union Shops List: Oregon and Washington (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Orange County Central Labor Council: AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Organization Staff ILGWU: Capacity and Availability Data Sheets, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Office of the Clerk, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- ORT: Organization for Rehabitation Through Training, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Local 215 Northwest D.C., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Pacific Northwest District Council: Merger, Resolutions, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Piece Rates and Add Ons in All Shops, 1965-1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Burt Pines, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Planning Ahead, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Plumbing and Pine Fitting Industry: Local 38, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Political Candidates, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Political Reform Audit Division, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Political Contributions, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Puerto Rico District Council: Locals 600-601, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Reich, Adell, Crost and Perry, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Reiner, Ira: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Remodeling: Office, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Reprints, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Restated Trust Indenture of Health and Welfare Fund, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Retiree Service Update, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Report on Union Busters Sheet: AFL-CIO, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Russo, Philip: Correspondence To and From, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- San Francisco Joint Board, 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Gan, Glenn, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- San Francisco Joint Board Contracts, 1971-1979 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  Scope and Contents
  Chinese
- San Francisco Joint Board: Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- San Francisco Joint Board: Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- San Francisco Organizers: Daily Report, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Scully, Charles: Attorney at Law, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- ILGWU Seminar, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Seminar: Apple Valley, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Seminar: Highland Springs, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Service Bureau Corporation, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Shop Assignments and List, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Sick Leave Policy, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Siems, Frederick: Executive Vice President, Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Southern California Apparel Industry Association, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Southern California District Council: Delegate List, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Southern California District Council: Minutes, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Local Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Spitz, Milton A.: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- State of California Employment Development Department, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Statement of Organization, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Illegal Homework [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Illegal Homework [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Montoya Law, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Homework, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 1 of 4], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 2 of 4], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 3 of 4], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 4 of 4], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 1 of 3], 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 2 of 3], 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Wolf, Max B. [folder 3 of 3], 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Wolf, Max B., 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Federal Ban on Homework, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Subcommittee on Garment Manufacturers, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Garment Industry Licensing Law, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Sacramento (Box 15, Folder 3)
- San Francisco, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- The "Bitter Salad" (Box 15, Folder 5)
- AB 353: Fact Sheet (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Licensing Law, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Labor Abuse, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Garment Manufacturers Act, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- "Sweatshop" Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Garment Industry in Southern California, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- SB 545 Amendment, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- The Case of a Garment Industry Licensing Law, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Union Newspaper Clippings and Documents, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Exploitation of Garment Workers [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Exploitation of Garment Workers [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- ILGWU: Convention, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Garment Industry, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Prosecution of "Sweatshops" [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Prosecution of "Sweatshops" [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Garment Worker Exploitation, 1975-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Andriola, Salvatore C., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Garment Industry: Licensing Law, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Garment Manufacturing Act [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Garment Manufacturing Act [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- The "Shortage of Help and Voluntary Compliance" Myth (Box 16, Folder 6)
- The Shame of the Garment Industry Continues (Box 16, Folder 7)
- California Labor Disputes [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- California Labor Disputes [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- The Case for a Garment Industry Licensing Laws, 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Community Relations Conference, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Subcommittee on Garment Manufacturing, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Garment Manufacturer Registration and Problems, 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- ILGWU: 37th Convention [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- ILGWU: 37th Convention [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Apparel Workers, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- SB 545 and Licensing Law [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- SB 545 and Licensing Law [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Garment Industry Violations [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Garment Industry Violations [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- California Labor Laws, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Senate Bil 545, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Montoya Law, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- A-1 Novelty Company, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Adrian Belt Company, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Alfar Imports, Limited, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- All American Trimming, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- All American Trimmings, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 1 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 2 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 3 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 4 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 5 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)